promocodes.co.uk 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy

Promocodes.co.uk takes your privacy very seriously and takes every reasonable precaution to safeguard the personal information you supply us with. Promocodes.co.uk is registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 under registration number Z9842529. The information you provide us with is safeguarded under the terms of this act.

### Personal Information

Promocodes.co.uk wants to ensure that the principals of "opting-in" are clearly explained. This means that when you sign up to receive email communications from us, you understand that you will receive promotional offers from Promocodes.co.uk and/or other selected third parties. You can unsubscribe at any time if you would prefer not to receive promotions in the future.

By registering with Promocodes.co.uk each visitor is opting in to receive regular offers via email, direct mail & telemarketing. These offers will be sent only by digitalbox Ltd, its partners or its clients. If you do not wish to receive such offers you can unsubscribe from the service at anytime.

The data that you provide is held by Promocodes.co.uk. Promocodes.co.uk holds your data in a central database and this database is only accessed by reference to interest or demographic categories in order to provide you with information about those interests you have selected. The process of supplying you with this information is at all times under the control of Promocodes.co.uk although specialist third party suppliers may carry out the dispatch.

### Partner Site Registrations

If you have registered with Promocodes.co.uk through one of our 3rd party partner sites, it is possible that they may also retain your data.

### Unsubscribe

You can unsubscribe from Promocodes.co.uk at any time according to your requirements through the unsubscribe link clearly displayed on all email communications.

The consequences of unsubscribing are that your account details will be placed in a suppression file and you will not receive any further email communications from Promocodes.co.uk.

If you need to contact Promocodes.co.uk regarding an unsubscribe request you can by emailing [unsubscribe@promocodes.co.uk](mailto:unsubscribe@promocodes.co.uk)

### Security

Promocodes.co.uk is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities.

Although we endeavor to ensure the security of all correspondence, the Internet is not a 100% secure medium. Therefore, we are unable to guarantee the security of any data you send electronically to Promocodes.co.uk and therefore cannot accept responsibility for any loss or damage experienced through any loss of confidentiality of information.

### Cookies

A cookie is small text-only file which is stored on your computer when visiting a site that record preference for that particular site's usage. Promocodes.co.uk uses cookies solely to enable us to identify you when you return to the Promocodes.co.uk web site.

The cookie will not allow a website to learn any personally identifiable information (such as your name and address) that you have not otherwise given to us. The cookie will also not track where you go when you leave promocodes.co.uk.co.uk or where you came to our website from. It's only purpose is to make your visit to Promocodes.co.uk easier and more rewarding for you.

The use of cookies in Promocodes.co.uk means that you do not have to enter information such as your log in name and password every time you visit the site, resulting in an improved login experience.

For example, Promocodes.co.uk may store your login details in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you log out. This cookie allows you to be automatically logged in the next time you visit Promocodes.co.uk. If you are using a public computer or do not otherwise want this information to be stored, you should log out before leaving the site. The sites or services you visited may store their own cookies on your computer. Promocodes.co.uk recommends that you read each site's privacy statement to understand their policies and practices regarding the use of cookies. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies using the settings on your browser. If you have cookies disabled in your browser you are still able to use the Promocodes.co.uk site but you will not have the benefit of an automatic login.

The functionality of Promocodes.co.uk depends upon your browser accepting session cookies. Promocodes.co.uk tracks visitors to and on the Promocodes.co.uk site by using referrer tracking. Promocodes.co.uk uses click thru and open mail tracking when sending emails. This process allows Promocodes.co.uk and its clients the ability to profile the recipients of their communications. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

It is possible to configure your web browser to refuse cookies or to be informed if a cookie is set. We refer to the manual of your web browser.

We will not use the IP addresses or cookies to identify you personally.

### Useful Information

Promocodes.co.uk adheres to all legislation laid out in The Privacy and Electronic Communications Act of 2003 as well as following UK best practice guidelines laid down by the DMA. We are keen to promote the best interests of consumers and how their personal data is used; for further information about data protection you can visit:

The Direct Marketing Association; www.dma.org.uk  
The Information Commissioner; www.dataprotection.gov.uk  
The Citizens Advice Bureau; www.adviceguide.org.uk

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact Promocodes.co.uk at:  
Promocodes.co.uk  
15 Gay Street,  
Bath, BA1 2PH  
To call us please phone 0044 1225 787 151
